[{"Question":" In which menu is the command to insert headers and footers available?","option 1":" File","option 2":"Insert","option 3":" Format","option 4":" Edit","answer":" Insert"},{"Question":" To print a document, press ..............then press Enter.","option 1":"Ctrl + N","option 2":"Shift + P","option 3":"Ctrl + M","option 4":"Ctrl + 0","answer":"Shift + P"},{"Question":"What is the default file extension used by Excel 2016 and later versions?","option 1":".xls","option 2":".xlsx","option 3":".xlsm","option 4":".xlsb","answer":".xlsx"},{"Question":"Which area in Excel displays the active cell address?","option 1":"Status Bar","option 2":"Formula Bar","option 3":"Name Box","option 4":"Ribbon","answer":"Name Box"},{"Question":"Which feature would you use to capture and analyze data from multiple sheets into one sheet?","option 1":"PivotTable","option 2":"Data Form","option 3":"Consolidate","option 4":"Template","answer":"Consolidate"},{"Question":"What is the quickest way to resize a column to fit its contents?","option 1":"Double-click the column header","option 2":"Drag the header","option 3":"Right-click and select resize","option 4":"Use Format options","answer":"Double-click the column header"},{"Question":"How would you quickly find all cells in a worksheet that contain formulas?","option 1":"Use Find feature","option 2":"Filter by color","option 3":"Go to Special","option 4":"Use Trace Precedents","answer":"Go to Special"},{"Question":"You need to track changes made by team members on an Excel workbook. What feature should you use?","option 1":"Track Changes","option 2":"Audit Trail","option 3":"Revision History","option 4":"Document Inspector","answer":"Track Changes"},{"Question":"How can you split text from one cell into multiple columns?","option 1":"Use Text to Columns feature","option 2":"Use DIVIDE()","option 3":"Use SPLIT() function","option 4":"Use SEGMENT()","answer":"Use Text to Columns feature"},{"Question":"How do you link data from a cell in one worksheet to another worksheet within the same workbook?","option 1":"Use the Link feature","option 2":"Type the cell reference directly","option 3":"Use a hyperlink","option 4":"Use a formula","answer":"Type the cell reference directly"},{"Question":"The measurement is not made in square metres in case of","option 1":"Form works","option 2":"Plastering","option 3":"Damp proof course","option 4":"R.C. Chhajja","answer":"R.C. Chhajja"},{"Question":"The main factor to be considered while preparing a detailed estimate, is","option 1":"Availability of Material","option 2":"Quantity of Material","option 3":"Transportation of Material  ","option 4":"All of the above","answer":"All of the above"},{"Question":"The unit of measurement of plastering is","option 1":"Cubic meters","option 2":"Square meters","option 3":"meters","option 4":"None of these","answer":"Square meters"},{"Question":"The unit of measurement for electric wiring or electrification light, fan, is","option 1":"Number of Points","option 2":"Type of Points","option 3":"Total length of wiring in meters","option 4":"Total power at mains in kW","answer":"Number of Points"},{"Question":"The plinth area of a building includes","option 1":"Area of the walls at floor level\t","option 2":"Area of cantilevered porch ","option 3":"Both A and B are correct","option 4":"None of the above","answer":"Area of the walls at floor level"},{"Question":"Calculate the volume of earthwork of a road for cutting having formation width 10 m and side slope 2:1 using Prismoidal method. The depth of road at chainage 0, 20, 40, 60 and 80 meters are 0.20, 0.90, 00, 0.80 and 1.00 meter.","option 1":"325","option 2":"425","option 3":"525","option 4":"625","answer":"625"},{"Question":"Calculate the volume of earthwork of a road for filling having formation width 10 m and side slope 1.5:1 using Mid-section method. The depth of road at chainage 400, 420, 440, 460,480 and 500meters are 1.10, 0.80, 0.90, 1.10, 0.60 and 1.50 meter.","option 1":"850","option 2":"1074","option 3":"1224","option 4":"1415","answer":"1074"},{"Question":"_________ is the analytical process of determining the current (or projected) worth of an asset or a company.","option 1":"Valuation\t","option 2":"Costing","option 3":"Estimation","option 4":"None of the above","answer":"Valuation"},{"Question":"Which is not a necessary knowledge for a property valuer- ","option 1":"Estimation and Costing","option 2":"Surveying and Levelling","option 3":"Computers and software","option 4":"Building by law and regulations","answer":"Computers and software"},{"Question":"Which of the following statement is True?","option 1":"Gross Income = Net income + Outgoings","option 2":"Gross Income = Net income â€“ Outgoings","option 3":"Net Income = Gross income + Outgoings\t","option 4":"None of the above","answer":"Gross Income = Net income + Outgoings"}]